ASHER PERUSCINI

A user interface/experience lead with a background in film production and journalism; Dual-citizen (British/American); can't learn enough; loves to draw; abdicated king; fiddler of new technologies; interested in cryptocurrencies since 2011; Formula 1 fanatic; moved all over the world since I was 4-years-old.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead UX Engineer/Designer - myKaarma

2015 - Present | Los Angeles, CA

myKaarma is a market leader in communication and payment software solutions for automotive dealerships. Joined as the first designer at the early stage startup with <\$1M capital raised. The company reached >\$10M in annual reoccuring revenue, in part from my drive of the company's entire design and user experience strategy, including designing solutions for enterprise customers in the U.S. and Canada (Audi, Mercedes,-Benz, BMW, and Porsche).

- Conduct Sprints, clients/stakeholder presentations, and user feedback reviews, leading to a 5x y.o.y. increase in payments made ().
- Spearhead the adoption and creation of user-flows and rapid prototyping with HTML/CSS/JS and interactive click-throughs, allowing for a three-fold increase in the product development cycle.
- Oversee usability testing, quality/code reviews, and provide technical/tech nological advice, resulting in a 92 net promotor score and 31.3 million customers.
- Implement user success metrics, like Mixpanel and Intercom, to make data-driven UI/UX decisions, culminating in increase user adoption rates and reduce tier-1 support tickets by 233%.
- Managing/mentor a team of two designers in developing user personas and scenarios to enhance functionality/usability testing across various product lines, aiding developers to increase understanding of product require ments in half the time.
- Conduct detailed research into governmental regulatory compliances, such as TCPA and GDPR, to design legally acceptable UX experiences.
- Creation and staged rollout of a comprehensive company design system allowing for design consistency across all platforms.

The Fun Stuff

- Slack Redact (Classified Mode)
- Delta cryptocurrency Apple Watch UI
- Otter Python SSH workflow for Alfred3
- Medium Play.ht Chrome Extension
- Walmart MoneyCard App

Front-End Designer & Developer - 5DayApp

2015 | Los Angeles, CA

- Designed, developed, and delivered responsive UI and UX experiences that leveraged various HTML/CSS/JS cross-platform frameworks, reducing time-to-market releases.
- Gathered user feedback and developed multiple iterations of lo-fi wireframes, mockups, and interactive prototypes, which led to a 29% bump in customer satisfaction.

Digital Media Manager - Music City Motor Cars

2014 - 2015 | Nashville, TN, USA

Freelance Web Developer

2007 - 2015 | Nashville, TN, USA

(615) 596-9059

asherperuscini@gmail.com

ashers.design

@redcoatasher

in @asherperuscini

@asherperuscini

EDUCATION

Northern Film School (Leeds Beckett University)

2002 - 2005 | Leeds, United Kingdom B.A. | Film & Moving Image Production

Middle Tennessee State University

2010 - 2014 | Nashville, TN B.Sc. | Journalism

SKILLS

Personas

User Scenarios

UX Design User Flows

Wireframing Sketching

Rapid Prototyping

Interview

Competitive Analysis Heuristic Evaluation

UX ResearchSprints

Usability Testing

SQL

Sketch

inVision & inVision Studio Photoshop/Illustrator/XD

Abstract

Figma Zeplin

OmniGraffle

Coding

Tools

HTML/CSS JS/jQuery GIT GWT

React Flutter Bootstrap